talenthouse.com 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Talenthouse

The Privacy Policy on this page is effective from August 3, 2015. You can find the previous Privacy Policy at this link.

**(Last updated on July 18, 2015)**

Welcome to this website offered by or in connection with Talenthouse, Inc. (collectively, "Talenthouse," "we" or "us") with an office at 306 North Robertson Boulevard, West Hollywood, CA 90048 USA. As used in this privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy"), the singular term "Website" refers to the talenthouse.com domain and any subdomain of talenthouse.com and the term "Services" refers to all websites (including without limitation the Website) and all devices or applications that collect personal information from you that we or our affiliated companies and their successors (a current list of which can be found here) ("Affiliated Companies") operate that link to this Privacy Policy, web pages within each such website, device or application, any equivalent, mirror, replacement, substitute or backup website, device or application, and web pages that are associated with each such website, device or application.

Please read the following to learn more about this Privacy Policy, which includes terms required for compliance with California Civil Code Section 1798.83. If you have any queries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting all personally identifiable information you may provide us through our Services. We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain what information may be collected in connection with our Services, how we use this information (including without limitation use by our Affiliated Companies) and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through our Services or through other means and devices described below and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions posted on the Website, sets forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Services. Depending on your activities when using our Services, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

We generally keep this Privacy Policy posted on the Website and you should review it frequently, as it may change from time to time. Any changes we make will be retroactively effective once the revised Privacy Policy takes effect (the effective date will be specified). If the changes that we make, in our sole discretion, are material, we will notify our registered users of the changes via email. You may object to the revised Privacy Policy prior to their taking effect, in which case we will delete your account and you agree to cease all use of the Services. Of course, you can always choose to terminate your use of the Services by notifying us of your desire to do so at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com), in which case we will disable or delete your account and any information we have stored that relates to your account, as set forth in Section I of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Services after such posting or notification will be deemed your acceptance of any changes to our Privacy Policy. WHEN YOU ACCESS THE WEBSITE OR USE OUR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN THE WAYS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO YOUR INFORMATION BEING USED IN THIS WAY, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING THE WEBSITE AND USING OUR SERVICES.

## A. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Our Services typically collect two kinds of information about you: (a) information that you provide that personally identifies you and (b) information that does not personally identify you that we automatically collect when you use our Services or that you provide to us.

  1. **Personally Identifiable Information** : As used in this Privacy Policy, "personally identifiable information" includes without limitation any information that may identify you, such as your first and last name, city and country of residence, email address, mail address, phone number, etc. As a general policy, we do not automatically collect your personally identifiable information when you visit the Website. In certain circumstances, we may request, allow or otherwise provide you an opportunity to submit your personally identifiable information in connection with a feature, program promotion or some other aspect of the Website. For instance, you may: (a) provide your name, city and country of residence, and email address when registering with the Website, or in connection with a contest entry; (b) provide certain demographic information about yourself (e.g., gender, usage frequency, etc.) when participating in a survey or poll or specifying your interests or profession; or (c) post a general comment and/or recommendation via our Services. Certain information may not be personally identifiable when standing alone (e.g., your city), but may become so when combined with other information (e.g., your city and first and last name). Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit or Service that we may offer, or gain access to certain content on the Website.

  2. **Non-Personal Information** : As used in this Privacy Policy, "non-personal information" is any information that does not personally identify you. Non-personal information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified by Talenthouse or a third party service provider, such as Google Analytics—i.e., information that has been rendered anonymous. We or our service providers automatically collect certain non-personal information from you when you access the Website. This information can include, among other things, IP addresses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari), the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista, Windows XP, Mac OS), the name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, NetZero), the search terms you use on the Website, the specific web pages you visit, whether you "love" a particular item on the Website and the duration of your visits. The non-personal information collected by or on behalf of Talenthouse may be linked to or associated with your account, along with personally identifiable information that we collect.

## B. HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

  1. **Personally Identifiable Information** : The personally identifiable information you submit to us is generally used to carry out your requests, to respond to your inquiries, to better serve you, or in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information. We may also use this information to later contact you for a variety of reasons, such as customer service, to provide service updates, to provide you promotional information for our products or services or those of our Affiliated Companies, to identify and target you for promotional activities as someone who may be interested in a particular product or service of Talenthouse or our Affiliated Companies, to communicate with you about content or other information you have posted or shared with us via our Services, to administer Creative Invites, to send you invitations to new Creative Invites, and to contact you if you are successful in any such promotion or competition.

  2. **Non-Personal Information** : We use non-personal information in a variety of ways, including without limitation to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities of a particular product or service of Talenthouse or our Affiliated Companies, to ensure that content is presented to you in the best way possible, to enable you to participate in interactive features on our Website, and to improve our Services. We may use your non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others. We may share your non-personal information with our Affiliated Companies and third parties to achieve these objectives and others, but remember that such information is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.

## C. OTHER USES & INFORMATION

  1. **Marketing** : We may use your personally identifiable information to contact you by email to notify you about our products and Services (and those offered by our Affiliated Companies). We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties for marketing of third party products or services without first obtaining your express consent.

You may ask us at any time not to use your information for marketing purposes by contacting us at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com) or by exercising your right to unsubscribe on the relevant communication.

  2. **IP Addresses** : An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are accessing the Internet. Web servers (computers that "serve up" web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When visitors request pages from the Website, our servers log their IP addresses. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to others, and to track the use of our Services. IP addresses may also be shared as provided in this Privacy Policy. IP addresses are generally not associated or linked to registered users of our Services.

  3. **Cookies** : "Cookies" are small text files from a website that are stored on your hard drive. These text files make using our Services more convenient by, among other things, saving your account authentication token and preferences for you. We may analyze the information derived from these cookies and match this information with data provided by you or another party.

If you are concerned about the storage and use of cookies, you may be able to direct your Internet browser to notify you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive. You may also delete a cookie manually from your hard drive through your Internet browser or other programs. Please note, however, that some parts of our Services will not function properly or be available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.

  4. **Email Communications** : If you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. We will not keep these emails for longer than we deem to be necessary for our business activities. For security reasons, we do not recommend that you send non-public personal information, such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account information, to us by email. However, aside from our reply to such an email or for the promotional purposes described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, it is not our standard practice to send you email unless you request a particular Service or sign up for a feature that involves email communications, the email relates to your participation in a contest or use of a Service (e.g., a Creative Invite, as described in the Terms and Conditions), we are sending you information about a Creative Invite or other Service in which you are participating (e.g., someone comments on a piece of artwork that you uploaded to the Website), or you consented to being contacted by email for a particular purpose.

  5. **Transfer of Assets** : We may share your information with our Affiliated Companies, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of all or a portion of our assets, reorganization, or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including, without limitation, personally identifiable information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us.

  6. **Other** : Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor or disclose any personally identifiable or non-personal information about you if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law, legal process or any regulatory requirement; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Services, or other users; (d) respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties; (e) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of users of our Services or the general public; or (f) enforce compliance with the Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy or any other applicable terms or rules.

  7. **Third Parties** : We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties such as our co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships (e.g., Talenthouse’s Creative Studio partners). We may also share your information with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, data storage and security) related to the operation of this Website and our Services, or by making certain Services and Website functionality available to our users (collectively, "Third Party Service Providers"). These Third Party Service Providers will only use your information to carry out their specific business obligations to us. A list of the material Third Party Service Providers is available here.

  8. **Your California Privacy Rights** : Residents of the State of California have the right to request from businesses with whom the California resident has an established business relationship a list of all third parties to which the business, during the immediately preceding calendar year, has disclosed certain personally identifiable information for direct marketing purposes. We are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year. To obtain this information you should send a request to [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com) with the subject heading "California Privacy Rights." In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California Privacy Rights Requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

  9. **Response to Do Not Track Signals** : We do not track our customers across third party websites and thus do not respond to Do Not Track ("DNT") signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content. Your browser may allow you to set the DNT signal so that third parties know you do not want to be tracked.

  10. **Creative Studios** : As part of our Services, we allow certain third parties to offer Creative Studios powered by the Talenthouse platform. This Privacy Policy also applies to the information collected from any such Creative Studios. Users who already have accounts with the Website can use that account to access any Creative Studio. Users who do not yet have accounts with the Website can register through the Creative Studio; doing so will both create an account on the Website and will give the user access to the Creative Studio. By registering or logging in to a Creative Studio, each user acknowledges and agrees that (i) this Privacy Policy applies to the information collected from such Creative Studio and (ii) such user consents to Talenthouse sharing with the Creative Studio partner the user’s first and last name, email address, city and country of residence, gender, whether you self-identified as an artist when registering your account, and the type of artist that you self-identified as.

## D. PUBLIC FORUMS

We may offer chat rooms, message boards, or similar public forums where you and other users of the Website and other Services can communicate. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including without limitation personally identifiable information) in connection with your use of these public forums. We may use personally identifiable and non-personal information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the effects of the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Services.

## E. WHERE DO WE TRANSFER YOUR INFORMATION?

We may transfer your information to, or store it in, countries located outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") which do not have as developed data protection laws. If we transfer your data to third parties in the United States (i.e., other than to Talenthouse or our Affiliated Companies), we will endeavor to only send the data to companies which are Safe Harbor registered and certified. It may also be processed by staff at our Affiliated Companies or by Third Party Service Providers. Please do not register an account or otherwise send us your information if you do not want it to be transferred to or stored outside the EEA. By providing your information to us, you agree and consent to us transferring to, and storing your information at, countries outside of the EEA (a list of which can be found here).

## F. CHILDREN

The features, programs, promotions and other aspects of our Website requiring the submission of personally identifiable information are not intended for anyone under eighteen (18) years of age.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from persons under the age of eighteen (18). If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 and believe that your child has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com). A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 may review and request deletion of such child’s personally identifiable information through the opt-out procedures in Section I as well as prohibit the use thereof.

## G. KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECURE

We have implemented security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including without limitation Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt the transmission of nonpublic personally identifiable information and other information to and from the Website. Our Third Party Service Providers may also utilize additional security devices such as firewalls, security patches, and anti-virus programs, to protect nonpublic personally identifiable information. Please be advised, however, that while we and our Third Party Service Providers strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. In the unfortunate event that your "personally identifiable information" (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we will notify you in the most reasonable manner under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification could impede a criminal investigation. From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.

## H. OTHER SITES/LINKS

Our Services may link to or contain links to third party websites or services that we do not control or maintain. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any third party website. We encourage you to note when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of all third party websites before submitting any personally identifiable information to them.

## I. CONTACT & OPT-OUT INFORMATION

A registered user may log in to the Website and disable his/her account through the user’s profile page. Disabling your account will render your profile page unviewable. However, we may retain your personally identifiable information and may reinstate your account (at your request).

In addition, you may contact us as at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com) if you: (a) have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy; (b) wish to make corrections to any personally identifiable information you have provided; (c) wish to disable or delete any information we have stored, including without limitation your account; (d) want to opt-out from receiving future commercial correspondence, including emails, from us or our Affiliated Companies; or (e) wish to withdraw your consent to our use or sharing of your personally identifiable information with others.

You have the right to see the personally identifiable information that we hold about you. You also have the right to access your information and should direct any request for your information to us at [support@talenthouse.com](mailto:support@talenthouse.com). Except where prohibited by applicable law, currently a fee of fifteen dollars (US $15) may be payable to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

We will respond to your request and, if applicable and appropriate, make the requested change in our active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that we may not be able to fulfill certain requests while allowing you access to certain benefits and features of our Services.

## J. SOLE STATEMENT

This Privacy Policy as posted on this Website is the sole statement of our privacy policy with respect to this Website and our Services, and no summary, modification, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, is valid unless we post a new or revised policy to the Website in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
